http://www.viu.edu/our-university/about-fxua/privacy-policy/

Academic Departments
BusinessComputer Information SystemsLanguage StudiesGeneral Education
Registrar’s Office
Academic CalendarAcademic CatalogCourse SchedulesRegistrationAdd / Drop CourseGrading System & GPAFERPAAcademic CatalogForms
Admissions & Aid
Admissions
Apply NowHow to ApplyAdmissions RequirementsEnglish ProficiencyAdmissions FAQs
Student Accounts
Tuition and FeesBilling and DeadlinesPayment MethodsPolicies1098-T FAQs
Financial Aid
Federal Financial AidTuition Payment PlanVeterans
International Student
Visa InformationCurricular Practical Training(CPT)Optional Practical Training(OPT)ISS ApplicationsISS FAQs
Student Life
Student Experience
Be INSPIREDBusiness AssociationsBusiness PartnersDiversity and InclusionHousingOn-Campus DiningStudent CenterStudent ClubsStudent EventsStudent ResourcesStudent StoriesTransportation
Career Center
Make an AppointmentTestimonialsProfessional ResourcesEmployment ResourcesEmployersPost Graduate & Internship Program
About FXUA
About FXUA
Board of TrusteesCorporate Advisory CouncilOffice of the PresidentAccreditationMembershipsMission Statement & PhilosophyUniversity TimelineConsumer Information DisclosureFacts and FiguresWhy FXUAAlumniInstitutional Effectiveness
Communications
Press ReleasesPhoto GalleryBrand
Human Resources
HR ServicesFaculty & Staff DirectoryEmployee BenefitsHR StaffOn-Campus EmploymentPolicies & ProceduresEvents CalendarJobs@FXUA
FAQ
CURRENT STUDENTPROSPECTIVE STUDENTALUMNI
Apply Now
How to Apply
Financial Aid
Programs
Academic Departments
Academic Catalog
Graduation
Fairfax University of America (FXUA) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our institution’s commitment to privacy. Fairfax University of America (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the website and mobile applications (the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Virginia Law
We protect our records in accordance with our obligations as defined by applicable Virginia statutes, including, but not limited to, the Virginia Privacy Protection Act of 1976, the Virginia Freedom of Information Act, and by any applicable US federal laws.
Information Collection and Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally, identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email address
First name and last name
Phone number
Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device (“Usage Data”).
This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
Fairfax University of America uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain the Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
To monitor the usage of the Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Fairfax University of America will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure of Data
Legal Requirements
Fairfax University of America may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of Fairfax University of America
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
Any changes made to FXUA’s privacy policy will be immediately available on this page. Users may visit this page at any time to view the most updated policy information.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement or the practices of this website – or if you choose to review or correct any information you previously submitted – please contact the FXUA webmaster at webmaster@fxua.edu.
Alert!
University update on the Corona Virus/COVID-19 Pandemic
FXUA commits to providing up-to-date information on its operational planning, safety measures, and resources for our learning community. Please visit our resource page for the most updated information.
×
